### **PROFILE**

I am a software Engineer passionate about technology with 3 years of experience in front-end development with Angular and reactive programming with rxjs. I focus on web technologies and development best practices.

Throughout my carreer path I have acquired knowledge in Typescript, javascript, Angular, React, css, HTML, sass, Angular Material, Boostrap and rxjs.

Experienced on team work using SCRUM methodology, azure and implementing practices like daily, planning, grooming and retrospective.

#### CONTACT

- alexandercordoba.dev@ gmail.com
- 318-408-3717

#### REFERENCES

## **CESAR DARIO CORDOBA**

Ing. Electrónico cel. 3152351239 Bogotá-Colombia

## **EDUCATION**

## **University Corporation Autónoma of cauca**

2020 Graduated with honors from the Autonoma University of Cauca.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **University Autónoma of cauca**

MAR 2019 - AGO 2019

 developed 3 software in angular 6 and Firebase together with the university seedbed. These softwares were registered in the national direction of copyright.

# SITIS – Soluciones Informáticas Integrales en Salud S.A.S

NOV 2019 - JUL 2020

• Frontend developer with Angular 10 and reactive programming with rxjs for hospital software.

#### **Asesoftware**

JUL 2020 - Present

\* Frontend Ssr Developer with Angular, rxjs, angular material, Bootstrap, Typescript and SCSS in banking, government and public transport projects.

## **SKILLS**

- I have advanced knowledge in Javascript, Angular and Typescript and intermediate knowledge in React.
- I master technologies like HTML, CSS and SCSS.
- I have advanced knowledge in Bootstrap and material design.
- I have knowledge in ionic with capacitor and angular.
- I adapt well to collaborative work with technologies such as git, github, jira and azure.